I want everyone to go on your knees for your country, continent and nation
and cry to God for redemption.
Now, it's everywhere.
Everywhere.
Dry bones shall rise again!
Whatever spots, whatever challenges - there is no single nation without challenges
and the challenges are causing uproar.
Right now, open your lips and say to the Lord,
"Here we are on our knees with humility, with all our heart.
I pray for my nation. I pray for countries. I pray for continents - troubled ones.
Father, come at this time and intervene."
Prayer For The Nations With Prophet T.B. Joshua
God's intervention
In the whole world
We need God's intervention
God's intervention
In the whole world
We need God's intervention
We're praying against
War in the whole world
War in Africa
We're praying against
The wrath of God on all our land
We need God's intervention
In the whole world
God's intervention
We need God's intervention
In the whole world
You've got the whole world
In Your hands
Don't forget the nations that rescue nations - they too are facing their own challenges.
Open your lips for prayer.
Prayer For The Nations With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Don't forget the nation, Nigeria. There's peace - that is why we're here today.
Pray for the leaders and the nation. Thank you. Hallelujah!
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Hallelujah. Thank you very much. Rise up!
RV: Mel Flowers 29/04/2019